{id: 1,
question: 'Race against your doubt, a lot of yall aint runnin fast enough. I can spot a fake before we even finish dappin up. Clappin when they win, but when I win, they never clap it up.',
answer_a: 'Drake',
answer_b: 'Russ',
answer_c: 'Lil Duval',
answer_d: 'Lil Wayne',
correct_answer: 'b',
detail:
},
{id: 2,
question: 'Pullin out the coupe out the lot. Told em Fuck 12, fuck SWAT. Bustin out the bells out the box. I just hit a lick with the box.',
answer_a: 'Mike Jones',
answer_b: 'Lil Blurry',
answer_c: 'Roddy Ricch',
answer_d: 'Vanilla Ice',
correct_answer: 'c',
},
{id: 3,
question: 'Maybe you dont understand what Im going through. Its only me, what you got to lose? Make up your mind, tell me, what are you gonna do? Its only me, let it go.',
answer_a: '50 Cent',
answer_b: 'Ja Rule',
answer_c: 'Post Malone',
answer_d: '2pac',
correct_answer: 'c',
}

const pop = [
    {id: 1,
    question: 'Toast to the ones here today. Toast to the ones that we lost on the way. Cause the drinks bring back all the memories. And the memories bring back, memories bring back you.',
    answer_a: 'Backstreet Boyz',
    answer_b: 'Maroon 5',
    answer_c: 'Selena Gomez',
    answer_d: 'Bob Marley',
    correct_answer: 'b',
    detail: 'Song: Memories by Marron 5',
  },
  {id: 2,
  question: 'If I knew it all then would I do it again? Would I do it again? If they knew what they said would go straight to my head. What would they say instead?',
  answer_a: 'Nsync',
  answer_b: 'Jack Black',
  answer_c: 'Lizzo',
  answer_d: 'Billie Eillish',
  correct_answer: 'd',
  detail: 'Song: Everything I Wanted by Billie Eillish',
  },
  {id: 3,
  question: 'Fifty-fifty, love the way you split it. Hunnid racks, help me spend it, babe. Light a match, get litty, babe. That jet set, watch the sunset kinda, yeah, yeah',
  answer_a: 'Justin Bieber',
  answer_b: '98 Degrees',
  answer_c: 'Ed Sheeran',
  answer_d: 'The Weeknd',
  correct_answer: 'a',
  detail: 'Song: Yummy by Justin Bieber',
  },
]

const country = [
    {id: 1,
    question: 'Well, I know whats right, I got just one life. In a world that keeps on pushin me around. But I stand my ground and I wont back down',
    answer_a: 'Hank Williams',
    answer_b: 'Johnny Cash',
    answer_c: 'Randy Travis',
    answer_d: 'George Strait',
    correct_answer: 'b',
    detail: 'Song: I Wont Back Down by Johnny Cash',
  },
    {id: 2,
    question: 'Yeah, Im gonna take my horse to the old town road, Im gonna ride til I cant no more. Im gonna take my horse to the old town road, Im gonna ride til I cant no more',
    answer_a: 'Garth Brooks',
    answer_b: 'Dolly Parton',
    answer_c: 'Foo Fighters',
    answer_d: 'Lil Nas X',
    correct_answer: 'd',
    detail: 'Song: Old Town Road by Lil Nas X',
  },
    {id: 3,
    question: 'So dont you worry your pretty little mind. People throw rocks at things that shine, and life makes love look hard.',
    answer_a: 'Reba McEntire',
    answer_b: 'Taylor Swift',
    answer_c: 'Blake Shelton',
    answer_d: 'Willie Nelson',
    correct_answer: 'b',
    detail: 'Song: Ours by Taylor Swift',
  },
]


const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Which statement about Hooks is not true?',
        answer_a:
            'Hooks are 100% backwards-compatible and can be used side by side with classes',
        answer_b: 'Hooks are still in beta and not available yet',
        answer_c:
            "Hooks are completely opt-in, there's no need to rewrite existing code",
        answer_d: 'All of the above',
        correct_answer: 'b',
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Which one is not a Hook?',
        answer_a: 'useState()',
        answer_b: 'useConst()',
        answer_c: 'useReducer()',
        answer_d: 'All of the above',
        correct_answer: 'b',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What Hook should be used for data fetching?',
        answer_a: 'useDataFetching()',
        answer_b: 'useApi()',
        answer_c: 'useEffect()',
        answer_d: 'useRequest()',
        correct_answer: 'c',
    },
];
